I can answer it now
Yeah yeah
Today is brighter than anyone else
It's the best feeling in my dreams
The excitement
Yeah yeah
I know
I know everything
About you and me
The spring of my head is too short
When your voice reaches me
I feel like I'm dreaming
Always
I'm grateful that I can meet you
The throbbing
Yeah yeah
The shimmering
The days I've forgotten
I feel like I can't even dream
The tears
Yeah yeah
The confusion
Hello everyone!
Good evening!
Merry Christmas!
KimeRoaR guaranteed
We areρ Curtis
Please show us a lot of love
Special Christmas news with real fun
Is there?
It Feels like Christmas
Right?
.This room is really cute
It has become a Christmas scene
That's amazing
Thank you for watching!
So, everyone, thank you for watching
today's show.
Today is the 3rd of April. What day is
it?
Today is the day when we make our debut
album.
No, it's the day when all the time is
wasted.
Please be careful.
I was suddenly called.
I was a little surprised.
We have a poster.
We did it!
Thank you!
Tomorrow is Christmas Eve!
So today is the day before Christmas!
It's Christmas soon, so please look
forward to it!
How many viewers are there?
691 viewers.
I'm so happy.
Thank you for 5,000 viewers.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
You can chat with us on Twitter.
You can tweet.
Is the volume okay?
It's fine.
The sound is not good.
The echo is gone.
Everyone is so cute.
The sound is not good.
The poster is here.
Manager.
It's here.
It's a cute poster.
It's like a house.
Yoko's house.
It's a live menu.
First, we would like to toast to the
release of Doki Doki Music Festival!
Let's introduce ourselves.
Maybe some of you are watching for the
first time.
I'm Munezu Kanamin.
I'm Murasaki Anzuya from the Super
Exciting New Year Club.
I'm Hitochan, also known as Hitoka
Osaka from the Super Exciting New Year
Club.
I'm Muruka Koizumi from the Super
Exciting New Year Club.
I'm Aki-chan, also known as Shida Aki
from Chou Tokimeki Lemon.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hiyori.
I'm Hiyori, also known as Yuri from
Chou Tokimeki Green.
Yay!
Hiyori!
It's the first time, right?
Hiyori's special camera.
I have a special camera.
Please, have a look.
It's a special camera.
Hiyori's special camera
KOTONE!
Roger that!
We hope you enjoy it!
Let's drink.
What do you want?
Peach and Muscat.
Who wants peach?
Peach.
Yes.
What does it taste like?
It's like amber.
It's beautiful.
I don't choose peach.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Did I put too much?
Anyone who likes it?
Yes!
Let's put a little less at first.
Is it okay?
There's another one.
Thank you.
That's nice.
It's tickling.
I was talking a lot last year.
I was talking a lot.
Cider?
Yeah, last year on top of food.
Chicken was sweet.
Oh!
It's open!
Pan pan pan pan.
It smells good.
It smells like a mask.
Can I have a cup?
Shall we read the comments?
Yes.
Cheers.
Flaming.
Cheers for the anniversary.
Who is this?
Everyone, please.
It's okay to drink.
It smells good.
Please turn on the sound.
December 23rd, we will release our
first album, Tokimeki Goods.
Please hold this cup.
Cheers!
The muscat is strong.
It's good.
How is it?
It's good. I drank muscat.
Oh, really?
I drank peach.
It's good.
Cheers!
I prepared a cider for December.
Oh, you prepared it.
Cheers!
Champagne!
We have champagne!
We have juice!
We have 800 viewers now!
I'm so happy! Thank you!
Thank you!
Please follow us on Twitter.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Please press the bell button.
Please follow us on Twitter.
Please follow us on Instagram.
Please take a picture of us and post it
on Instagram.
Really?
That's good.
Good morning.
I'm going to sleep.
It's time to sleep.
We're close.
The moment you're on Twitter,
you can post a picture of yourself.
Here.
Should I open Twitter?
I think you're on Twitter.
Where?
Are you on Twitter?
You can post a picture of yourself.
And,
I'll tell you what I've been up to
lately.
I'm a big fan of Master.
She went back to shop on Christmas but
Her body muscles were like
Better than before
She even went on diet
And tried to lose weight
We'll go through the lyrics
What about Yuyuko?
For example, recently I dropped a
flower on Kana's head.
Waffle chicken?
I heard a great voice.
Waffle chicken is a dish with chicken
on top of waffles and maple syrup.
I was wondering what it would taste
like, sweet or salty.
It was very good.
The waffle was crispy and the chicken
was salty.
The balance of sweet and salty was
good.
It was very good.
The chicken on top was also very good.
It was a good match.
I usually don't sit there, but I
sometimes sit there.
I want to eat it.
That's what I want.
That's right.
I want to eat something, not food.
I'm OK without food.
I was so excited watching this stream.
I was so happy.
Huh?
What was that?
I was so happy.
Please tweet anything you want.
The members might introduce the tweet
later.
Yes.
Please tweet as many times as you want.
Please tweet a lot.
I'll put it on right away.
Really?
Ramen!
It's delicious!
Great!
It's a lot of eggs.
It looks delicious.
The members are eating it all by
themselves.
I'm jealous.
I love eggs.
This is cute.
Can I read it?
The moment I got excited recently, I
was a nursery teacher.
A crybaby in the nursery told me,
I won't cry anymore when I get married
to my teacher.
That's great.
Thank you.
I've been listening to this since I was
little.
What would it be like if I were an
adult?
It's so romantic.
I'm going to tell you.
I love you.
I won't let you go.
I'm so excited.
I'm going to tell you.
I don't know.
You can do whatever you want.
I want you to comment on the chat.
Please write on Twitter.
Let's read the chat.
Please write a hashtag.
Please.
!!!
Dun dun dun is what I'm sure if I'm
right
Dun dun dun is what I might say
Wow...
Dun dun dun is what I Sould Say
Dun dun dun is what I say
It's time for Ruki to start
She was all ready to sing
No Мар engages in talking
I wasn't ready
What did I just sing just now?
I'm so happy!
I met Tsuda Aki-chan!
I met Minami-chan!
Haruka is the cutest!
What's so funny?
I'm not smiling.
Haruka is the cutest!
Thank you!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Yeah!
It's started!
Hiori's Oh My God! T.U.K.M.J!
It was fun!
It was great!
It was the best!
It was fun!
It was great!
I was a little bit nervous.
Hiori was a little bit nervous.
See you again!
Please watch it when it's over.
And when I was doing my best with my
bare face,
Hiyori-chan was laughing with her
shoulders like this.
It was funny.
That's funny.
We always appear in the U-JIBU, so we
only did the behind-the-scenes.
Everyone, please leave a comment or a
Twitter after the live.
Bye-bye!
Anime!
No!!
Well then, I'll go next!
So this time has been a super heacity
all the Natsuhime Riko's first solo
debut
So, we'll show everyone, musicals a bit
ahead of their solos
Here they are!
strands of strands
I've already whispered
Strand!
Strands.
Strand?
Ah.
To Strand...
I love you!
That's weird.
I found it!
I was waiting for it.
I won't let go!
Once I bite it, I won't let go!
Let's do it!
Let's go back to the beginning.
Let's start with this.
Let's start with Kagamin.
I'll start.
I'll introduce the songs in order.
The first song is...
Tumorou!
Yes, that's right.
Um, yes, that's right.
Before that, here's an video of my
album.
It's dangerous.
We just sang when we introduced
ourselves.
We haven't even gone to sleep yet.
Let's have pizza.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Next Episode Preview
Always look at me
My precious feelings
Forever and ever
I think I can be by your side
Please subscribe to my channel!
I don't think I can achieve my dreams
Give up or be confused
Right now, call me back, call me boy
Let me hear your voice, sing a song
If you fall in love,
Shake it up! Shake it up!
Feel good, shake it up!
The number of layers is like a love
bootcamp
Lose weight, lose weight, lose weight
Don't forget to replenish water
I won't let go
Lion Girl
Shake your hair
Run through the wilderness
Lion Girl
A beauty scream
Beautiful eyes, July cider
The night you spilled it
I can't forget it at any time
It hurts, it hurts
I want to erase my painful everyday
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I walked alone.
I remember the pain of the journey.
It's because of this summer
I'm not sure if I can say that I'm
scared or that I'm crying
Let's go, go, let's go, let's go
forward with our voices out!
If you're feeling down, let's go
together
Let's go, go, let's go, let's go
forward with our voices out!
If you're feeling down, let's go
together
One, two, three, we can overcome
anything
Go! To the future!
Let's go! We are the delivery girls!
Let's fly! Aiming for your heart!
Like a butterfly, DASH! Like a bee,
SING!
We'll sneak in and steal it!
Let's go! We'll always run through with
all our might!
We'll engrave the meaning deep in our
hearts!
Hey!
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colorful
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I draw a fragment of the future
It will guide me
Because I fell in love with you
Love will soon turn into love
A simple happiness that's only complex
My heart is satisfied
I want to stop more
It's a pain, this feeling
Your shaker
Spin more, spin more
Spin more, heart shaker
It's good.
So, we've watched the teaser.
This video will be uploaded to APEX's
YouTube channel by the end of this week.
So please look forward to it.
Now, let's look back.
I think I said my name earlier.
It's okay.
Ta-da!
M1, the strongest set of the world!
The strongest set!
Hello! Hello!
I'm so excited!
This song is our first single and also
our first single.
It's a song that makes you feel
positive and positive.
We get energy from this song when we
perform live.
I think this song will give courage to
many people.
I think many people have listened to
this song.
The music video is also uploaded.
Please listen to this song a lot.
Let's listen to the second song.
The second song is...
See you at Shibuya!
This is the first time I'm performing
at K-Town SuperFu.
I've also performed in front of you at
the Yukan concert.
I'm sure many of you have heard it
before.
The best part of this song is the
melody.
The lyrics are very...
When you think about yourself,
you can feel a lot of things coming to
your mind.
There are many lyrics that you can
relate to.
The lyrics are...
This is it!
This is a really good song.
I hope you listen to it more and more.
I hope you can make it a better song.
I've heard it 5,000 times.
Wow!
It's a great song!
It's a good song.
It's Shibuya.
Fabrin is...
That's right!
Is there anyone who likes it?
I'm sure there are people who have
heard it.
I want you to tweet it.
I'll read the comments.
I'll say,
It's amazing that you're going to
Shibuya Tsutaya by yourself.
That's right!
It's an official song.
It's an official song of Shibuya
Tsutaya.
I remember the choreography.
Wow!
It's something you can easily
choreograph.
The dance video is also uploaded to
YouTube.
Please watch it.
There's a shuwa in it.
That's right!
Next, please.
What I'm going to introduce in the
world is...
Drum rolls!
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta!
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is the first song I've ever heard
from Taneguchi Maguro.
It's a lead song of this song.
I'm glad.
Did you all watch the music video?
I saw it.
Everyone is so cute.
It's not just cute, it's a little sad.
It's a music video that's a mixture of
everyday life and non-ordinary life.
It's a great music video no matter how
many times you watch it.
If you haven't seen it yet, please
watch it a lot.
This song is really...
It's a song that tells you that there's
no ceiling on the second floor.
It's a pop song that anyone can listen
to.
Let's listen to this song a lot and get
excited together.
Everyone posted a picture of us
meeting.
I'm wearing a bubble wrap.
It's funny.
It's a very sad picture.
I'm crying.
The part of Endless Calamity makes me
cry.
Thank you.
I'll replay it.
I saw it on Twitter.
I love Hito-chan's tears so much that I
can cry.
Endless's music video is too good.
It's too good.
The person who posted a picture of us
with Pabrin is taking pictures.
I'm still there.
You can take a picture with us, so
please take a picture of us.
It's rare.
I can't take a picture with you all the
time.
I don't need money.
I took a picture with Pabrin.
I want to go to the toilet, but I
can't.
If you like, please take a picture of
us.
I'll play the fourth song.
The fourth song is this.
It's a super version of Koe no Seipan.
Super version is a new song that AKI
added.
AKI's voice is also included in the
super version of Koe no Seipan.
A new shape up has been released.
I wonder if anyone has heard of it.
Koe no Seipan is a diet song for
dancing and singing.
When I first heard this song, the staff
told me to lose weight.
I thought it was a song.
It's a song that makes you want to move
your body.
My cousin is listening to this song in
the bath.
In the bath?
It's a song that makes you feel like
you're going to break.
It's a song that I recommend to people
who want to lose weight.
I was running when I couldn't work
outside.
I often ran while listening to Koe no
Seipan.
I thought I had to lose weight.
It's hard to lose weight.
It's a song that can be exciting even
at a live concert.
Please look forward to it at the live
concert.
I really lost weight.
I'm fine.
I ate a lot.
I ate hamburgers and steaks in the
morning.
It's not a hamburger.
It's a hamburger and a steak.
After the lesson, I went home and ate a
hamburger.
I'm fine.
I ate a gratin.
I ate a teriyaki that my mother ate
after that.
I ate a lot.
Everyone, I'm eating in the bath.
Don't worry.
Next song.
M5? M5!
Lion Girl!
This is a new song.
Did you listen to Lion Girl?
This song is a new style that we
haven't done before.
It's a song about a strong girl.
We will never let the advertisers go.
We will keep singing this song.
We can't show you our dance yet, but
it's fun.
And you can be like this.
Please look forward to it.
You said you wouldn't let go.
You listened to it.
I did.
Some people listened to it.
Some people listened to it yesterday.
After Hito-chan's line, there are many
people who say,
「More! Johnny!」
I listened to it on earphones the other
day.
I don't know the lyrics.
Please listen to it on earphones.
Next.
The 6th song is...
「Saija of July」
All the songs are good.
There are many members who like this
song.
It's a popular song.
It's a collaboration song with Natali.
It was created by the song.
It's a song written by Okurei Sakuno.
It's a song about a summer love.
It's a song that comes straight from
the intro.
There's a point that Aki-chan likes.
Yes.
My favorite point is...
The end of the chorus and the end of
the second chorus.
The part where you say 「Ah 」 is not a
hiragana.
Look at the lyrics.
It's not a hiragana.
I think it's good to use kanji.
Please listen to it while looking at
the lyrics.
The dance is also a point.
I haven't shown you yet.
No.
It's better to enjoy the dance.
Well...
What was that?
It's a cute dance.
So please enjoy it.
Please enjoy it at the live show.
Shizuoka-chan wrote 「Bo」 before.
What is 「Bo」?
I made a mistake.
It's my part.
I drank it all.
It's a cute hint.
It's scary when you're young.
Lion girl also said this.
「Tatte ga miyurashite」
I'm embarrassed.
This is not good.
It's too detailed to be transmitted.
This is Shizuoka.
I can't hide it.
I can't control myself.
I'm embarrassed.
Next is Sakura-san.
Please look forward to the next video!
This song is provided by Aoi Yamazaki.
This song is a song that comes to my
mind when I hear it in the time of April
or farewell.
It's a song that I'll be separated from
my friends while looking back on the
memories of various schools.
But it's a song that pushes me back to
the next future.
It gives me a lot of courage.
I'm going to do my best to go down the
path I've chosen.
It's a song for those who are looking
forward to their graduation.
The choreography is also very good.
It's not just a sharp dance, but it's
also a bit flexible.
It's a song that shows a little
feminine side.
Don't switch here.
It's a special song.
I'm lonely.
Let's go to the next song.
The camera has changed.
It's a song that everyone sings in the
chorus.
It's a song that's been a hit in the
spring.
There were a lot of solos.
It's a song that's been a hit.
It's a song like this.
Let's read the chat.
The comments are fun.
Is it a special camera for spoilers?
It's a special camera for spoilers.
I'm going to say everything that comes
out.
It would be nice if you could see the
water.
I saw a comment saying that I like
Sakura.
Please write a spoiler.
You don't have to read the chat about
spoilers.
I like Sakura.
I like Haachan.
I like Lion Girl.
I'm looking at something else.
Are you on Twitter?
Please tweet.
Please tweet a lot.
Please add two.
Please add a lot of tweets.
It's a trend.
I'm graduating next spring, so I'll
listen to Sakura a lot.
I'm going to listen to Sakura's
graduation song.
Let's move on to the next song.
Please tell your friends to listen to
it.
Please tweet.
It's a funny spring.
Next, I like the dance of the song.
Please look forward to it.
Next is the victory story of Super
Akimeki Senren.
This is a song that has a power-up on
the title and song title.
This song is also a song that has Aki's
voice in it.
It's a long song.
The song was called Victory Story.
The name is also a song that will
continue to walk the path of victory.
This song is also a song that will
cheer you up.
Please listen to the new version of the
song.
Please look forward to the victory
story of Toki-kun.
Are you going to do it?
Thank you for watching.
Come here.
I'm still young.
What's going on?
You're cute.
You're good.
You're fresh.
You have more friends.
Come here.
Welcome.
You're the leader.
I'm the leader.
May I listen to it?
I'll listen to it.
You're cute.
delivery store!
Also, you can discuss in this place.
Dubai Toyů
Thank you Arigato.
Yaaayee!
Yay yay yay yay!
We've performed this song many times,
but it's a song that we're really
excited about.
It's a song that you can enjoy without
thinking about anything.
This song was provided to us by
the member of the group, Nanigiri-san.
It's a song that has a lot of members
in it.
So, let's cheer up and be energetic
today!
I'm saying what I like.
Ryoshikawa-san, you like what you say.
And also,
we're eating, right?
The 21st century of Harapeko.
There are a lot of members in the
lyrics.
And not only the song,
but also the dance has a lot of
highlights.
Karumin is showing off her acrobatics.
And Julia is showing off her
throbbing...
fan!
She's showing off her throbbing fan.
And Hitoka, Haru, and Piyo are
doing something that I'm really into.
Did you notice?
It's the first time for the third
generation.
I'm the main melody.
That's right.
And who's the lowest?
I'm the lowest, and Piyo is the main.
And Takahito is...
I thought I was the main.
That's a good thing.
I thought I was the main when I was
smiling.
I didn't expect that.
I thought,
but I didn't want to make a mistake.
So I said, yes.
It's embarrassing.
Why are you so careful?
I'm the highest?
I didn't think I was the highest.
I thought either of us was singing
higher.
No, no.
Too high.
Opera?
Center?
I laughed too much.
But there are so many good songs.
I don't know if this is a good song.
Please look forward to it.
Let's move on to the 10th song.
The 10th song is GAMUSHARA's Super
Version.
This is the first GAMUSHARA with Aki's
voice.
As the title says, it's a GAMUSHARA
song.
It's a GAMUSHARA song.
It's a song that sings about us.
We are also working hard every day.
It's a song that cheers up the hearts
of GAMUSHARA.
Please listen to it.
Aki, you're not in the picture.
Let's move on to the next song.
Next is M11's Ameagari.
It's a new song.
It's Ameagari.
Did you listen to it?
Everyone, please listen to this intro.
This intro is also very cute.
It's like walking in a puddle.
I only listened to the title song of
this song.
I imagined walking in a puddle with an
umbrella.
Then the title song is called Amemari.
I thought it was a very nice song.
This song is a song that says, even if
your heart is cloudy like rain, it will
definitely be sunny, so it's okay.
It's full of very positive lyrics.
The lyrics are very cute.
It's a very cute lyrics that says, play
the rainbow piano or wear the rainbow
dress.
Please listen to a lot of lyrics and
songs and cheer up.
I'm looking at Twitter.
Hitochan part of GAMUSHADA is cool.
Thank you.
I want to play the piano with you.
Are you a person who can play the
piano?
I want to play with you.
When I hear the song, my heart becomes
clear.
I'm glad to hear that.
Let's listen to the last song.
The last song is...
We love you all!
We are Seishun Heart Shaker!
We love you!
Everyone knows how we react to the
live.
What do you mean?
I don't care anymore!
We haven't seen it yet.
It's been a long time.
What's that?
It wasn't on the screen.
It was on the screen!
You're so good at it!
We are Seishun Heart Shaker!
No, we're not!
We were like this just now.
Everyone, you haven't seen us yet.
Look at us.
We're looking at the floor when it
starts.
We are Seishun Heart Shaker.
What's that?
Speaking of the song, it's a mix of
love and spirit.
Of course, it's a great song.
I'll make you laugh!
I can't remember the song.
The fans are watching.
I don't usually do this, but...
I like Heart Shaker more.
I'm going to cry.
Isn't the word Heart Shaker really
good?
It's good.
It's a heart-shaking dance.
There's a choreography where we shake
our bodies.
We say, turn it more and more.
There's a lot of choreography that we
can do together with the main dancer.
Do you do this song?
Do you do this Heart Shaker?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Do you do it?
You do it, right?
You can't say that.
I'll do it.
You don't know, do you?
I said it as the leader.
I'm the leader of the leader.
I'm so nervous.
Please give me a towel.
That's how you become a leader.
I'll pull it out.
Lala Lala
Don't open it.
I'm doing it slowly.
It's fun to have so much fun.
I introduced it earlier, so I'll
introduce this.
It's in my hand.
Tissue is in my hand.
This is so fashionable.
Please hold this one by one.
There are six, so please introduce
them.
I haven't introduced Hiori yet.
Let's introduce it together.
What is Kanami's?
This is a flower everyone has.
This is a flower from Saitama Super
Arena.
The live CD is being recorded.
Yes, it's a live version of Tamawari
Kiku.
We'll see it later.
We'll introduce it later.
We'll be performing Tamawari Kiku live.
We'll see it later.
How about this side?
What is this?
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
The sound source of the live
performance is recorded as a CD.
You can listen to it while imagining
the live performance.
It's the first time for Toki-san to
listen to the sound source of the live
performance as a CD.
If you come to the live performance,
you can listen to it while imagining the
live performance.
If you haven't come to the live
performance yet, you can listen to it
while imagining the live performance.
Please listen to it.
Next, this is the CD.
This CD is a CD that you can watch the
video of ZEPP HANEDA, which we did at
the debut live show.
I can't see it well.
If you can see it, please take a look.
There is a picture of how it was.
Please take a look.
This CD is amazing.
This is amazing, too.
Please take a look.
What is the first one?
This is a picture of everyone holding
flowers.
This is a picture taken from above.
This is a video of the live performance
at the Saitama Super Arena.
The live performance was held at the
Saitama Super Arena.
If you haven't seen it, please take a
look.
I saw it a while ago.
What did you see?
I saw it.
What are you looking at?
I made a little arrangement.
Please take a look.
I saw it.
This is cute.
What about Julia?
This is Julia.
Please take a look.
It's okay.
Let's take a look at the intro later.
Which page?
Is there something in it?
No.
Can't we show this?
Did you put it out?
No.
Maybe there's something that's not in
it.
No, maybe I'll twist it once.
There's something that's not in it.
It's in the menu.
I see.
She's coming!
I see!
You're so cool!
I'm trying to make it up.
I just got it.
Some people don't know what I'm talking
about.
I'm not wrong.
You're sweating.
I'm always on Twitter.
You're always free.
I want to open it soon.
I have this.
This is the limited edition of the
song.
This song, DVD, and the making of the
music video of Endless.
And the booklet.
I heard that this box is famous.
Right?
It's a box!
I saw it and I thought it was a box.
I thought it was a box.
I'll open it.
This is a good one.
You shouldn't spoil it.
I'll show you the cover.
No, no, no.
You shouldn't do that.
This is the DVD.
It looks like this.
It's small.
You should put it here.
No, no, no.
You'll get scolded by adults.
This is the DVD and CD.
This is a special box.
Let's see the CD.
The people who received this will get
the booklet.
I want to open it.
There's a sign on it.
It's amazing.
You shouldn't show that.
It's great.
It's nice.
It's amazing.
This is a booklet.
Bath?
That's too much.
You are a luxury man.
It's a music video.
I see.
Bath.
I'm a man of man.
You are a man of man.
No one wants to see it.
I want to see it.
I'm embarrassed.
It's a broadcast accident.
Next is the first live of us.
It's a HANEDA KIKO KIKO version.
Listen to it.
It's not a live video.
Please listen to it.
Is it free?
Is it okay?
I'm nervous.
Please listen to it.
I'm going to be scolded.
Everyone will want it.
This is the last one, the heart-
throbbing version.
All 12 songs are recorded naturally.
If you listen to all of these songs,
you'll be in the natural zone.
It's blue.
Please check out all the phones.
Now, let's move on to the broadcast
section.
It's time for the broadcast section.
Let's go to the broadcast section.
First, let's broadcast with DiverCity.
DiverCity is doing a great job.
Let's go to the natural zone.
Please look forward to the next
broadcast.
Here we go!
Super exciting channel
All Night Tokimeki Japan
It was really the best!
It's fun
It's a test
It seems like we can go to the test
This is a test
Then let's call
Next is RIVENCITY
T-shirt
Thank you!
Good evening!
Let's say hello to Suzuki-san.
Where should we look?
If we look this way?
This way.
Let's go!
To Suzuki-san's heart,
Rock on!
We are Super Doki Doki Senpai!
Thank you!
Oh, this!
There are a lot of people outside.
Wow!
Where are we now?
We are at the store!
It's before the store, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
Music video is playing.
It's so big.
It's big.
Great.
And this cute jacket.
I like it.
I'm glad.
Inside the store?
They will show us inside.
Great.
Awesome.
Isn't it amazing?
It's hard to see.
It's so cute.
Look at this.
If you buy it at this store, you can
get a special receipt.
Please check it out.
It's so cute.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad to see the costume.
I'll give you this costume.
Thank you for your purchase.
I heard a lot.
By the way, which is your favorite
costume?
My favorite...
Well...
This is a very good one.
It's a white costume.
Cute.
Yes.
Thank you for giving us a lot of ideas.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
Great.
The goods are also...
Yes, I like this one.
It's cool!
It's a CD.
Wow, it's our CD!
I'm so happy!
Is this poster random?
Can I get a poster of my favorite
singer?
The poster is random.
We drew the autograph.
Thank you for your autograph.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you for coming to see us.
Thank you for watching our live.
Thank you.
Please continue to support us.
Please go and watch our live.
Do you have any favorite songs?
Do you?
I like all of your songs, but I like
the one from July the most.
You're popular!
I like the one from July the most.
I like the choreography, so I hope
you'll watch it.
I hope you'll come to our concert
someday.
Please come to our concert! We'll be
waiting for you!
I'm sorry.
Time lapse.
I'm a little lonely.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you.
One year special show.
So, do you have any tweets that made
your heart flutter?
I'll check it out.
I saw a good one.
The husband is washing the dishes.
Husband, please wash the dishes for
your wife.
The world will be filled with
excitement.
Let's do it.
Let's make it peaceful.
Please wash the dishes.
It's Christmas.
Let's fight.
Do you have any tweets?
Meat.
Steak.
That's what makes my heart flutter.
It's a video.
I'm waiting for it.
She said, I wash the dishes every day.
That's kind of you.
I'm excited.
I went to Ura-Oten.
Thank you.
It's a Tenbo by Yamiyoshi.
I got a message!
I'm a boyfriend who has been dating
since I was a student.
I'm going to propose to you.
Congratulations!
Yeah!
Yay!
Congratulations!
What is this?
I can't stop clapping.
I want to have a surprise wedding with
the PR staff someday.
I want to have a surprise wedding.
I want to go to the wedding.
I want to change the name of our
company.
It's interesting.
Hiyori is interesting today.
She is always interesting.
She is the best today.
Everyone is saying congratulations.
She is kind.
She is washing the bath.
She is very kind.
I want you to say that you are warm.
It's good.
It says that she made a new person.
I want to have another person.
I see.
Another person?
It's her.
She is doing her best in front of
Shibuya.
She is our official character.
She is doing her best.
She is doing her best for the special
event.
She is OPAV.
She is waiting for you.
What is she holding?
What is it?
It's Starbucks.
Starbucks?
It's a waiting time.
That's right.
It's the waiting time.
There is a Cinderella time.
It's until 8pm.
It's a break time.
You can still make it in time.
Please come and see us.
Please come.
The pillars are amazing.
It's reproduced.
It looks like it's going to be hard.
It's dangerous.
It's a bit scary.
She is breathing.
The pillars are amazing.
It's a bit scary.
It's okay.
You can go back to your normal
position.
What is it?
It's cute.
It's warm.
You've been doing it for a long time.
Someone has to say it.
Show me the pillar.
It's the 26th.
It's the day of the big event.
Thank you for the announcement.
You want to see the pillar, right?
Is there a pillar?
Show me the pillar.
Can you turn right a little more?
This posture is quite warm.
I'm sleepy.
Paburi!
Paburi, do your best until the end!
See you!
Thank you!
Paburi!
December 20th?
If you can make it to the 20th, please
meet up with Paburi!
Please take a picture!
Now, we'd like to do a project here.
It's called, Improvised Quiz for
Christmas from members!
In this clip, there is a quiz that you
guys came up with for Christmas.
The winner of the quiz will be given a
hand-mail with our autograph!
We are doing a quiz on Twitter, so
please tweet the answer to this quiz!
I'll start with Tanabin.
Merry X'mas fromíz
It is the birthday of my crush, Maofuu
Dando!
Thank you!
How was it? Did you get it?
Follow us on Twitter!
Cute.
Next, Julia.
What is Julia's favorite food?
What cake will Julia eat this
Christmas?
This is a cake.
This is a woman eating a cake.
This is a twin tail.
Next, Hitoka.
What do I prepare for Christmas?
That's the question.
Can you tell us the name of the member?
It's easy to understand.
My quiz is...
I eat paella at home every Christmas.
Which country's food is paella?
Please write the country's name.
This is a good question.
Let's move on.
Next, I'll answer.
What color was the macaron on the
Christmas cake last year?
What color was it?
It's difficult.
My birthday cake was a cheesecake tart.
It was a cheesecake tart cake with a
macaron on top.
This year, it was orange, yellow and
white.
What color was the Christmas cake last
year?
I see.
Next, Hiori's quiz.
This is Hiori's quiz.
What was the present that Hiori asked
Santa Claus for his childhood?
What do you think it is?
It's a present I asked for when I was a
kid.
How old was I?
I think I was three years old.
I see.
I got a hint.
What is it?
It's a hint.
It's scary.
It's okay.
Please do your best.
Let's read the questions one by one.
I'm going to read the question.
What day is it in the lunar calendar?
What cake are you going to eat this
Christmas?
What do I prepare for Santa every year?
I eat paella at home every Christmas.
Which country's food is paella?
I know this one.
I don't know.
I just want to know.
I'm going to eat the macaron which was
on the cake last year.
What is the Christmas present that
Hiori asked Santa Claus for?
Please write down your answer, name of
the member and the answer.
You will get a hand bell.
We will sign it.
Please sign it.
I got a purple macaron.
How is it?
I'm sorry.
Tio got a Pikachu doll.
That's close.
That's the answer.
Purple macaron looks delicious.
Pink?
Please write down your answer, name of
the member and the answer.
See you soon!
I thought it was Keroro.
Tadurin?
I will ask Tadurin to be a guest.
She is not here today.
She will be here.
Tadurin!
Inokura!
Please come to this show!
I will come back.
The woman behind me will be here.
I will be here.
Ida-san!
Can you hear me?
Ida-san from Spire!
Hello!
It's the last song!
Let's do a greeting to Ida-san.
I don't know what to do.
Let's do it. I'm sure you can feel it.
Ready, go!
To Ida-san's heart, rock on!
We are Super Doki Doki SNS!
Thank you!
Yes It was so much fun, thank you for
so many come back~!
Bye bye!
Everyone!
I wonder if there is a little...
There is a little noise.
I want to tell you with Tablin
telepathy.
Tablin!
Please do it.
I understand.
Yes.
I'm kidding.
Bye-bye!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for coming back!
See you again!
Thank you very much!
I'll come back someday!
Please come to the shop.
Yes!
Thank you very much!
I'll come back someday.
The time is coming.
Yes!
I'm sure you'll have the most fun here.
Me!
Let's eat cake together!
You?
I was looking forward to it.
This is next.
Next?
I'm looking forward to the cake.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to eat it.
Let's eat cake!
Cake!
I wonder if the answer is coming.
I've been waiting for a cake.
I want a hand mirror that can be
signed.
I wonder if it's possible to sign it
like this.
Hito-chan, cookie.
Aki-chan, green.
Aki-chan is also quite difficult.
I'm looking forward to it. Cake, cake.
I wanted to eat spring cake.
Before eating cake, let's drink
alcohol.
Let's go.
Cake.
It's a cake.
Do you wear a belt?
Yes, I do.
I'll put it here.
The skirt is too big.
Thank you.
Staff is the priority.
Not member.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Aki-chan.
This is great.
You have 4 members.
If you have a cake, please prepare it.
I don't know if there is a cake.
I eat a lot of cake recently.
With Aki-chan.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Let's take a picture together.
Look at this side.
Cute.
I like it. Thank you.
I'll have a cake.
I'm glad. Thank you.
Everyone!
Itadakimasu!
Bon Appetit!
R Quèr X Kahler
Took the AirPods chasing us
Now, we have AirPods
Let's go,
The footsteps we've heard
It's the moment when you eat it.
When we eat, nothing is interesting.
Let's be careful.
Let's eat.
It's great.
It's delicious.
Wow, it's hot.
It's a special way to roll it.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
I'll eat it.
Do you want to eat this?
Julia, please look at the camera for
the sake of spring.
Talk to me.
For the sake of spring.
I'm not eating the rice gruel. I'm
eating the spring roll.
She's looking at the camera.
How is it?
Thank you!
I'm Yukako.
Can I have some of Akita's sweet red
bean?
Please subscribe to our channel.
Cute.
It's dangerous.
Strawberry is the best.
The last one was a cake?
I love you.
We are in the same age.
Don't wait for the switching.
Do you want to eat strawberry?
The back is noisy.
I won't give you.
Cute.
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's delicious.
I wonder if anyone has a cake at home.
That's right.
It's amazing.
I wonder if anyone has a birthday on
Christmas.
I think so.
I want to be announced to the north.
I want to be announced to the south.
I'm eating it, but it's okay.
I want to eat it.
Do you want it?
Cute!
I think it's dangerous.
If you put on a costume, it's like a
short cut.
That's true.
I want to go to the short cut.
Hiyorin, you're cute.
Let's go to Kaname.
I'm waiting for you.
The bird is weird.
Why?
Chickens Abby&Elena
So, we did it in 5 people.
So, Koizumi-san will be the last one.
Why?
Everyone, you have to decide.
Everyone is waiting.
Why?
Haruka-chan!
This is weird.
Really weird.
Why?
I'm not going to do it.
Why? I really hate it.
I almost ate the strawberry.
I'm going to put the strawberry on it.
I'm going to put it on.
Well, then...
Are you serious?
Until you get it.
3, 2, 1, go!
Do you want it?
I'm happy.
OK, that's all.
You just said, Hana.
I'm sorry.
It's long.
It was the best.
No, no, no.
Show us the result of your practice.
I didn't practice anything.
Let's do it together.
Ready, go.
OK.
지고ova
The hood of that bandit who asked for
reliable decree
The cake is falling
the lemon
Took the candy
Haruka, I love you!
Thank you.
The cake is delicious.
Yes.
Delicious.
I can't stop eating it.
Tomorrow is Eve.
I bought a cheesecake.
I ate it today.
Really?
I ate it little by little.
I want to do a cake one-hole challenge.
Delicious.
Amazing.
Do you eat strawberry first?
I eat strawberry last.
I know.
I feel fresh when I eat strawberry
last.
I eat strawberry together.
Strawberry?
1, 2, 5, strawberry.
I know this!
It's nostalgic.
Eh?
It's okay.
Stand in front of the camera.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Thank you for the meal.
That was fast.
Hito-chan's strawberry song.
Please listen to it.
Strawberry song.
I think it's a bit too much.
Strawberry, strawberry, strawberry,
strawberry, how about one?
Thank you for the meal.
Cute.
The song is gone.
Thank you.
When is the next live?
This is... strawberry, strawberry,
strawberry, strawberry, well, 2,150
people are watching.
January 5th.
It's my birthday.
I'm telling you.
January 15th is also my birthday.
January 15th.
Oh, yeah.
It's my junior's birthday.
January 15th.
Why am I being taken?
It's scheduled to be released in two
days.
You gave us a quiz earlier.
Give us a hint.
Hint? Do I have a hint?
I don't know.
Thank you for the meal.
What kind of hint do you like?
One!
One is a hint?
The hint is that it's a day that
everyone is looking forward to.
Thank you.
It's a question related to Christmas.
It's almost there.
Everyone is answering correctly on
Twitter.
What about you, Juri?
My hint is...
I think it's something I like.
That's right.
I ate it last year.
That's all.
There's no one who said that.
If I say this, everyone will know.
What about Hitoka?
I have two.
I will say one.
I don't want to say.
What should I do?
Secret?
Secret.
I will say that I have two.
If you tweet me two, it's correct.
Not one, but two.
Is this a hint for the impromptu quiz?
Yes.
My hint is yellow.
I thought it was Twitter.
Yellow.
I think I got it.
Yellow and red.
Yellow is good.
I got it.
Yes.
What is my color?
Oh, I see.
I can't tell you the color.
Oh!
I don't know.
Hiyori-san!
I really don't know.
Hiyori's hint for a small doll is that
hint and the name starts with PO.
I told you!
The name starts with PO.
It's a small doll.
Let's call Paburi again.
Paburi!
Can you hear me?
Bye!
Good evening!
Everyone!
Hello! Good evening!
Thank you!
Let's talk a little more.
It's already cut off.
It's cut off.
It's quite difficult.
It's a live broadcast.
We will greet Iida-san properly
someday.
Maybe there is still a chance until 8
o'clock.
The last 15 minutes of the time limit.
We are the first to enter.
We are the second.
I'm looking forward to it.
This is a present.
I've been waiting for this.
It's a very special day.
We bought Christmas presents within the
time limit.
We haven't seen the contents yet.
What is this?
Let's shuffle.
Is it okay to take it off?
Let's go to the last minute.
What kind of feeling is good?
Please come inside.
How should I draw?
Can you do it?
Yes.
I'll draw it randomly.
Kuro will draw it too.
I heard that you can see the inside of
the dress.
So, I'll draw it according to the song.
Then, I'll draw it according to the
song.
Staff will give you a signal.
Let's start.
Let's do the opposite side.
Let's do it slowly.
It's a victory story.
It's heavy.
It's light.
It's very light.
Oh, here it comes.
This is...
It's quite long.
Let's do it in reverse.
This is our song, so let's do it again.
This song never stops.
The one you have now?
This one.
Let's open it.
Is it yours?
No, it's not.
It's not.
It's mine.
It's yours.
Mine?
One more time.
But it's...
It's going to be mine.
Should we shuffle?
Let's do it one more time.
Should we shuffle and turn it?
Please look forward to the next video!
Oh, that's it.
What?
1, 2, 3, jump!
This is fun!
It's good!
I hope this time will continue.
I hope this precious time will
continue.
It's not stopped!
Something is not stopped.
Let's start walking again.
It's not stopped!
It's a coincidence of a chance.
Who is it?
Stop!
It's not my song.
It's not.
It's over.
We should continue this time.
Let's go to the endless.
Let's go.
It's fun.
This one?
Not this one.
It's yours.
Let's spin one.
Spin it with your own bounce.
If you spin one, everyone gets white.
This is mine.
Let's spin the other one.
Let's spin one more.
Let's spin this one.
It's yours.
It's not fair.
Let's do it randomly.
I'll give you this one.
It's not about the round one.
This is not white.
It's mine.
Is this one OK?
The song is not finished yet.
What's this mess?
I'll give you this one.
It's not mine.
I got it.
I ignored the round one.
What's this?
I'm curious about the comment.
It's a mess.
I laughed.
I can't stop watching.
Which one do you want to open?
Let's open this one.
It's cute.
What should we do? Should we say who it
is first?
Let's not say.
Let's guess.
But we might know who it is.
Ta-da!
What's inside the box?
What's this?
I think we know who it is.
Ta-da!
What's this?
What's inside the box?
So cute!
Do you know who it is?
It's Oharu.
It's the cute flower bouquet from the
first episode.
Doesn't it look like me?
It might look like you.
It's like an animal.
Kanamin said she wanted a bouquet with
her name on it.
So Oharu is here.
She's always with me.
The pink case and the chupa chups
are...
I don't usually buy them.
I thought it would be nice.
So I bought them.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to this channel.
We look alike.
I'll take you anywhere with my pet.
I'll take you to a live show.
I hope you'll put it on my costume
someday.
I'll take you to Tokikuri.
Next, Julia.
Who is it?
I saw a package.
What is it?
Aroma sticker for mask.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Lavender herb.
Where do you put it?
She found out.
This is from me.
This is a mask.
It's not lavender.
It's a mask sticker.
I forgot.
This is a mask that sterilizes the
environment.
It sterilizes the air.
You can use it as a mist.
You can use it as a mist for the air
and the mask.
It has a very nice scent.
It smells fashionable.
It sterilizes the air.
How is it?
Does it smell good?
Yes.
Thank you!
Next is Hitoka!
What is this?
There is something like this in it.
It's cute.
What is this?
You are laughing a lot.
Thank you!
I'm glad I like this chocolate.
What is this?
I'll open it.
I'm looking forward to opening it.
What is this?
It's a picture of Aki-chan.
I was found out.
Everyone, this is Aki-chan.
The clerk is taking good care of me.
It's Pakkun-chan.
I don't know if she'll be happy.
I'm very happy.
Really? Thank you.
What is this?
There is a box inside the box.
This is a Louis Vuitton City.
It is a Louis Vuitton City and a
D-Store.
It is a Louis Vuitton City in Denmark.
I love Louis Vuitton City and I always
drink it.
The lyrics of Lion Girl also contain
the lyrics of Louis Vuitton City.
I made it a Louis Vuitton City for
everyone to drink it.
I will drink it after taking a nap.
I am glad. I like tea very much.
I was addicted to tea.
Thank you very much.
The chocolate is a bonus.
I found it at the store and brought it.
I love chocolate.
I am glad. Thank you.
It is fashionable.
Everyone is fashionable.
I will open this.
Who is this?
It is big.
It is a red bag.
Who is this?
It is a pen.
I am glad. I like it.
I can see the name.
It says by Hiyori.
This is a gift for spring.
It is a gift from Hiyori.
I will open it.
What is it?
It is big.
Yes, it is.
What is it?
It is quite a lot.
What is this?
Is it a memo?
What is it?
Is it a tomato?
It is a tomato.
Wow!
It is cute!
It is like a room-air.
It is a chopsticks.
I wanted to buy this chocolate for
everyone.
Is that so?
It is a chocolate and a milk.
Can I open it?
Thank you.
It is cute.
It looks like a doll.
It looks like a girl.
Look!
It is cute.
Please take a picture.
This is my second time to take a
picture.
It is cute.
It is a rainbow.
Thank you.
I will take a TikTok video with this.
I am a member of staff and a senior
member.
I can't see the fun side of senior
members.
This is cute.
This is a pajama.
Thank you.
I can see the strength of the female
power.
I wanted a pajama.
This is warm.
This is warm. I am happy.
Thank you.
Who is this?
I'm going.
Wait.
This is...
What?
Kanami?
Oh, no!
I'm so happy!
Wow!
This is the one we were talking about
earlier.
I was like, huh? I bought this!
I'm so happy!
It was a little heavy.
Yeah, it was heavy.
The light.
The actress light.
I forgot to bring the mirror.
Oh, yeah.
You should reflect it.
Put it in the bag.
Aki-chan's makeup is better.
Yeah.
I'll bring the mirror.
Everyone uses a mirror.
I'm glad.
I'd be happy if I got this.
I don't buy it often.
I'd like to give a brave present.
There's a page in it.
You can use it later.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry for the pajamas.
I'm glad.
The last is Hiyori.
Who chose this present?
It was fun last year.
I'm serious this time.
This is it.
Can I say something?
It's a convenient size.
It's easy to use.
I don't think Hiyori has much.
Really?
I'm serious.
There's no candy in it.
Last year, I bought a chocolate in the
shape of a rugby.
I'm serious.
What is it?
It's cute.
So cute!
There's nothing in it.
Wait a minute.
There's something in it!
Fried chicken!
Open it!
She's just made a decision.
There's fried chicken in it.
It's good.
I can't eat it.
I'll open it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Great!
You are good at speaking Japanese.
What is that?
What is this?
Open it.
Can I open it?
I got it.
This feeling is...
Where is it?
I love this square.
Try to open it.
It's a low-resolution.
Low-resolution?
Low-resolution is good.
It's good.
Cute.
I ate both cake and chicken.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
It's cute.
I don't need to buy a squeeze.
Right?
You are a good girl.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
It's fun. 965 people are watching.
Wow, amazing. We'll reach 1000 soon.
Thank you.
Shall we read some comments on Twitter?
Let's read some.
Jiria likes weird things.
No, I don't.
Cute.
Skin squeeze?
Yes, squeeze.
It's squishy.
It's soft.
Thank you.
I used to have this when I was little.
It was a squeeze.
It was popular.
Julia, your hands are in the way.
There's nothing in it.
Did you think it was an iPad?
I thought so.
It's amazing.
I thought it was a 3D printer.
I thought it was because I increased
it.
I added one zero.
I thought it was a 3D printer.
And she was a genius.
I'm so happy.
Everyone is so good at this.
Julia chose a serious one this time.
I chose a serious one.
Wow.
Are you coming?
Please give me a present too.
I'll exchange presents with my
boyfriend tomorrow.
I'll put a picture in it.
Wow.
You can do it, Kana-chan.
Okay, so earlier, Tsutaya, Chibuya
Tsutaya-san,
I'm not talking about the family,
but I'll connect you again.
Earlier, it was Sato-san from Tsutaya-
san,
but I'm going to make a call.
The video was not good,
so I'm making a call.
Let's say hello to everyone.
Students love collaboration projects.
Yes.
Good evening.
Hello?
Hello!
I'm Sato, a half voice friend of
Shibuya Star.
Sato-san!
Hello!
Please say hello first.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
To Sato-san's heart, rock on!
We are Super-Tekimichi-Sendai.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about earlier.
I'm sorry.
It's perfect now.
It's perfect.
Thank you for having Shibuya Tsutaya-
san.
Thank you.
It's also in the official song.
I'm so happy.
Thank you for the official song.
Thank you.
Today, we were able to
sell it
outside.
Thank you.
Do you have a favorite song
from Tokimeki ga Subete?
Favorite song?
Well, I think it's the official song of
the company.
By the way, there are 6 girls in the
album.
Who do you think is the cutest?
Well...
I think it's Momoka.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
I've decided.
Wow!
I thought it was definitely not.
Thank you very much.
It was a great spring.
Tsutaya Shibuya,
Thank you for your continued support.
We will also sing
I will sing the official song.
Thank you.
I'll go play again someday.
Please do.
Can I have a word at the end?
Anything is fine.
The product has been launched once,
and in the second stage,
We have a copy of the recommended one
We're preparing it.
We hope that all the fans will come
to the second floor of Tsutaya Shibuya.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Okay, it's time to reveal the answers
to the quiz.
I'll go first.
I asked what day is Aiken Kuma's
birthday.
The answer is...
Tokikuri!
December 26th is Aiken Kuma's birthday.
There were many correct answers. Thank
you so much.
Next, Juri.
Juri's question was,
what cake will I eat for Christmas this
year?
Juri's answer is,
ice cream cake!
Ice cream cake!
I'm glad I said that.
Juri loves ice cream.
Next,
I asked what I prepare for Christmas
every year.
I gave you two hints.
One was cookies,
and the other was milk tea.
Milk tea!
I know that.
Really?
I prepare cookies and sweet milk tea
every year.
So, I'm sure you know the answer.
I don't think so.
These two hints.
My answer is,
Spain!
I said the country of the country,
but it's Spain.
Spain.
Akita.
I asked what color macarons I eat for
Christmas last year.
The answer is,
white!
I got it right!
What?
I'll get the answer right this time.
I'm not sure.
Next,
I asked Kanta,
who has the youngest memory of Hiori.
I asked what I prepare for Christmas.
I gave you four hints.
I said,
Popo!
So cute!
I asked Popo.
I think she's about three years old.
Did I get it right?
We'll draw a lottery to get the
handbell with the correct answer.
Thank you for watching!
Please pray for us!
We'll draw the handbell later.
Let's check out Twitter.
Thank you for tweeting.
We're doing a retweet project on
Twitter.
If you haven't done it yet, please
answer the questions.
You can get a limited edition of the
album.
Yes, it's a special Christmas album.
Lastly, let's say a message to each of
you.
Please listen to the songs in the album
with gratitude.
And also, let's say your aspirations
for TokiKuri.
Kanon-san.
Thank you so much for today.
Tokimiki was able to release all the
songs.
Please listen to the songs in the
album.
We were able to release a lot of songs.
It was a day that will remain in our
memories.
Today was a fun day because we
exchanged presents.
The actual Christmas is December 26th.
Let's spend a wonderful Christmas
together.
Let's spend a good day together.
We have no ceiling in our dreams.
I hope we can make more dreams come
true.
Let's share a lot of wonderful
excitement together.
Please continue to support us.
I'm waiting for December 26th.
Please watch the live broadcast.
Today, we are so happy to be able to
celebrate the release date of our album
with so many people.
We are so happy to be able to have a
fun Christmas party and release date of
our album.
As Kanami said, we are so happy to have
so many people supporting us at the
record shop and other places.
This is the first album since we
started APEX.
It's the first time for us to release
an album.
We were wondering how it would be.
We have 12 songs including good songs.
You have been listening to our new 5
songs since yesterday.
We are looking forward to the next
album.
We are preparing to make it the best.
We will make it the best.
Let's meet on the 26th.
We will do our best.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching the live stream.
I exchanged presents, ate cakes and
drank a toast with everyone.
It was very fun.
Today is the first day of the album
release.
I'm happy to spend such a fun time.
It's the first time for me to promote
my album.
I can release an album because of the
supporters.
Thank you very much.
There are a lot of good songs.
I think you've heard it.
There are a lot of cool, moving and
refreshing songs.
If you have the album, please listen to
it.
We will perform a lot of songs on the
album.
Please listen to it and prepare.
We are doing our best to practice and
rehearse.
Please look forward to it.
Thank you for watching the live stream.
Today is the release day of Tokimeki Ga
Subete.
We are very happy to release an album
in this season.
We are happy to release an album in
various stores and to support various
people.
We have a new song for the first time,
a song that is reborn with AKI's voice,
and a lot of other songs.
Please listen to it.
We also exchanged Christmas presents.
I want to take a picture with this.
We will do our best to give you
presents on the 26th.
If you haven't got the ticket yet,
please take a look at the live stream.
Let's spend the best Christmas
together.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much for watching the
live stream today.
I'm very happy to be able to share a
cake with you and exchange gifts.
And today is the release day of our
first album, Tsukimiki.
I'm so happy to be able to do this with
Pabrin.
I hope you will continue to support us.
I'm so happy to be able to do this with
everyone.
Tsukimiki has a lot of different
genres.
Thank you, Pabrin.
Please listen to our songs a lot and
love them a lot.
Please tell us your favorite song in
this album in the comments or Twitter.
And this week is coming soon.
Please listen to it with everyone.
Thank you very much for today.
See you next time.
We're on a business trip.
So, today is the day when all the songs
of TOKIMEKI are released.
Did you enjoy it with us?
The day when the songs are released is
so gorgeous.
Last time, we rode a bus.
You're laughing a lot.
This time, we read the comments
together like a Christmas party.
I was really happy to be able to
connect with you.
We put all the TOKIMEKI in all the
songs.
I hope you enjoy listening to them and
performing them live.
We'll also perform this song after
three days.
We'll also perform the song that we eat
cake and chicken.
We're having a lot of fun.
Hiyori's forehead is getting thinner.
Your cheeks are getting thinner.
I think there are some people who are
streaming, so we're having a live show.
Please come to Nakano Sunplaza and feel
the true feeling of TOKIMEKI.
We look forward to seeing you in three
days.
Thank you for today.
Thank you for watching today.
Thank you.
We will meet you through the screen.
Next, we will meet you through the
screen.
Let's meet through the screen.
Thank you.
Please support us.
Then,
We are Jyoteki Meki.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
We will do our best.
See you.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!